Aderinsola Jolaosho is a creative problem solver with experience in online and offline branding and public relations. She holds an MSc in Media and Communication from the Pan-Atlantic University and a Bachelor’s degree in English from the University of Lagos. She is also a pioneer at the Joseph Business School, Lagos.

She has worked in the real estate, hospitality and franchise development sectors. She has also facilitated sessions on communications, branding, digital marketing, public speaking, and marketing at Guaranteed Trust Bank Training School, Philip Consulting, Lotus Bank Training School and Billionaire Realtors’ Group Academy and a lot more. Aderinsola is passionate about helping businesses and individuals thrive. She is currently the Managing Partner of ThePush.ng.
